https://www.wineracks.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Menu
Wood Wine RacksWine Cellar RacksPrestige Series Wine Racks6.5 Foot Wine Rack Kits7 Foot Wine Rack Kits8 Foot Wine Rack KitsBase Wine RacksUpper Wine RacksAccessories and TrimComplete Cellar SystemsPine Wine Rack KitsTabletop Wine RacksHanging Wine RacksStackable Wine RacksWine Drawers
Metal Wine RacksVintageView Wine RacksW Series Wine RacksVino Pins and RailsEvolution SeriesCase and CrateVintageView TabletopCountertop Wine RacksHanging Wine Racks
Choose PayPal Credit at checkout for more details
Retail Wine DisplayWood Retail Wine RacksWire Retail Wine RacksVintageView Retail Wine RacksAluminum Retail Wine RacksMetal Shelving & Gondolas
Choose PayPal Credit at checkout for more details
CoolingWine Cellar Cooling UnitsWine GuardianWhisperKoolHow to Choose a Cooling UnitWine Fridges and CellarsAllavino Wine FridgesSummit Appliance Wine Fridges
Choose PayPal Credit at checkout for more detailsAccessoriesWine Accessories and GiftsRolling LaddersWine Cellar DoorsReal Stone Veneer and PanelsLED LightingDesign ServicesResidential Cellar DesignRetail and Hospitality DesignTrade Partner ProgramHow to Build a Wine CellarDesign Galleries
Account
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
WineRacks.com Inc. knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting WineRacks.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does WineRacks.com Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at WineRacks.com. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store features, and communication with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our website.
E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more productive to improve service and your shopping experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products, notifications of changes to our policies, and order confirmations. We may provide your email address to third party providers that perform advertising or email services on our behalf as well as to facilitate shipping and the processing of an order. Each of our promotional emails contain a link to Unsubscribe from our mailing list. By clicking the unsubscribe link, you will be permanently removed from our mailing lists. You can also use our contact form and tell us to Unsubscribe you from our mailing list.
What About Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. This website tracks users anonymously. It uses cookies, both first party cookies and third party cookies, to measure your usage of this website. This website tracks visitors using first party logging and reporting features as well as Google Analytics.
Does WineRacks.com Share the Information It Receives?
We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely neccessary in order to complete your transaction and order.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you provide to us for purchasing of our products or services. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer.
Which Information Can I Access?
WineRacks.com gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit WineRacks.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of New York. If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough description through our Contact Form, and we will try to resolve it.
Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
Information You Give Us
You provide most such information when you search, buy, order, post reviews, or other methods of communication via our website or email to WineRacks.com. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers, and credit card information.
Automatic Information
For security purposes WineRacks.com sometimes collects and analyzes the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, and to our website. This is done for your protection for tracking purposes in the unfortunate event that someone gains access to your personal or financial information and opens an account, or makes purchases under your name.
Questions
Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by Contacting Us directly.
JOIN OUR MAILING LIST!
Receive a 5% off coupon in your email. Simply signup for our mailing list!
*May take up to 15 minutes to receive coupon*
*Accessories and Cooling Products do not qualify for 5% OFF code
WANT A DISCOUNT?
ONE STEP CLOSER TO 5% OFF
*May take up to 15 minutes to receive coupon*
SIGN UP
SIGN UP FOR NEW ARRIVALS AND INSIDER-ONLY DISCOUNTS
Copyright © 2020-present WineRacks.com, Inc. All rights reserved.
